[{"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和1相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 1, "add": [{"add": 10, "result": 11}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和2相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 2, "add": [{"add": 9, "result": 11}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和3相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 3, "add": [{"add": 8, "result": 11}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和4相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 4, "add": [{"add": 7, "result": 11}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和5相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 5, "add": [{"add": 6, "result": 11}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和6相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 6, "add": [{"add": 5, "result": 11}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和7相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 7, "add": [{"add": 4, "result": 11}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和8相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 8, "add": [{"add": 3, "result": 11}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和9相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 9, "add": [{"add": 2, "result": 11}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和10相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 10, "add": [{"add": 1, "result": 11}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和11相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 11, "add": [{"add": 0, "result": 11}, {"add": 1}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [12, 13, 14, 15, 16], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和1相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 1, "add": [{"add": 11, "result": 12}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}, {"add": 16}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和2相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 2, "add": [{"add": 10, "result": 12}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和3相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 3, "add": [{"add": 9, "result": 12}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和4相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 4, "add": [{"add": 8, "result": 12}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和5相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 5, "add": [{"add": 7, "result": 12}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和6相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 6, "add": [{"add": 6, "result": 12}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和7相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 7, "add": [{"add": 5, "result": 12}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和8相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 8, "add": [{"add": 4, "result": 12}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和9相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 9, "add": [{"add": 3, "result": 12}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和10相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 10, "add": [{"add": 2, "result": 12}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和11相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 11, "add": [{"add": 1, "result": 12}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和12相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 12, "add": [{"add": 0, "result": 12}, {"add": 1}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [13, 14, 15, 16, 17], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和1相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 1, "add": [{"add": 12, "result": 13}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}, {"add": 16}, {"add": 17}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和2相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 2, "add": [{"add": 11, "result": 13}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}, {"add": 16}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和3相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 3, "add": [{"add": 10, "result": 13}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和4相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 4, "add": [{"add": 9, "result": 13}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和5相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 5, "add": [{"add": 8, "result": 13}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和6相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 6, "add": [{"add": 7, "result": 13}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和7相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 7, "add": [{"add": 6, "result": 13}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和8相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 8, "add": [{"add": 5, "result": 13}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和9相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 9, "add": [{"add": 4, "result": 13}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和10相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 10, "add": [{"add": 3, "result": 13}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和11相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 11, "add": [{"add": 2, "result": 13}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和12相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 12, "add": [{"add": 1, "result": 13}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和13相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 13, "add": [{"add": 0, "result": 13}, {"add": 1}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [14, 15, 16, 17, 18], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和1相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 1, "add": [{"add": 13, "result": 14}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}, {"add": 16}, {"add": 17}, {"add": 18}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和2相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 2, "add": [{"add": 12, "result": 14}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}, {"add": 16}, {"add": 17}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和3相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 3, "add": [{"add": 11, "result": 14}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}, {"add": 16}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和4相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 4, "add": [{"add": 10, "result": 14}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}, {"add": 15}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和5相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 5, "add": [{"add": 9, "result": 14}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}, {"add": 14}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和6相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 6, "add": [{"add": 8, "result": 14}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}, {"add": 13}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和7相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 7, "add": [{"add": 7, "result": 14}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}, {"add": 12}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和8相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 8, "add": [{"add": 6, "result": 14}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}, {"add": 11}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和9相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 9, "add": [{"add": 5, "result": 14}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}, {"add": 10}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和10相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 10, "add": [{"add": 4, "result": 14}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}, {"add": 9}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和11相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 11, "add": [{"add": 3, "result": 14}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}, {"add": 8}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和12相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 12, "add": [{"add": 2, "result": 14}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}, {"add": 7}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和13相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 13, "add": [{"add": 1, "result": 14}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}, {"add": 6}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}, {"body": [{"title": "加法计算，和14相加", "stem": "加法计算，和", "type": "au-fill-add", "augend": 14, "add": [{"add": 0, "result": 14}, {"add": 1}, {"add": 2}, {"add": 3}, {"add": 4}, {"add": 5}]}], "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "1", "answers": [15, 16, 17, 18, 19], "knowledges": ["20以内的不进位加法"], "number": "1-7-6-15"}]